

#### CONTACT

- coreyhamat@gmail.com
- **(**647) 998 1981
- www.coreyhamat.me
- Toronto, ON

#### **SKILLS**

#### **WEB DEVELOPMENT:**

HTML5 | CSS3 | SCSS | JavaScript (ES6+) | jQuery | RESTful APIs | Firebase | React | Gatsby | Building Accessible Websites | Version Control | Git & GitHub | Paired Programming | Team-based Development | Project Scope Management | Google Analytics | Programmatic Banners | GraphQL | Contentful | Veeva

#### **CREATIVE SKILLS:**

Vectorworks | Adobe InDesign | Adobe Photoshop | Adobe XD | Figma

# EDUCATION JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY

2021

- Web Development Immersive Certificate
- Web Development Con-Ed
- Accelerated JavaScript

## RYERSON SCHOOL OF PERFORMANCE

2014 - 2020

Completed 39 credits towards
BFA in Performance Production

#### **ABOUT**

I enjoy building websites that focus on accessibility & responsiveness. In addition to my professional developer experience, I have prior experience in technical theatre, and have developed a sharp attention to detail & excellent communication skills. I bring the ability to work directly with clients, listen to their needs attentively, and bring their vision for the project to life!

#### **PROJECTS:**

#### PERFECT PLAYLIST PROCUREMENT

React | RESTful API | SASS | Firebase

GIT REPO | LIVE

Using Deezer's API, a user adds a random song from a selected artist to a global playlist. Users can search for artists by genre, or by searching for their name

#### THE DIGITAL CINEPHILE

HTML | SASS | CSS | JavaScript | RESTful API

**GIT REPO | LIVE** 

A movie/TV recommendation app, built with the TMDB API, which displays a gallery of recommended movies and/or TV Shows based on user input. The website uses multiple API calls to display each recommended film's/TV Show's poster, official trailer (if available), user rating, and plot overview.

#### THE NYGMA MACHINE

React | RESTful API | SASS | Firebase

GIT REPO | LIVE

A randomly generated maze game that, when completed, shares a piece of advice, provided by the AdviceSlip API, based on a keyword selected by the user. The user earns a score, based on the number of steps they take to complete the maze, and the difficulty they selected, which is either displayed on a "Hall of Fame" or "Hall of Shame"

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

Klick Katalyst | Jan 2022 - Nov 2022

• Created clean, client-side code for fully-featured web applications, banner advertisements, and interactive visual aids (IVAs) in a fast-paced agency environment while collaborating with editorial and quality assurance teams to ensure the projects met the clients' requests and followed the important regulations for advertising pharmaceutical products.

#### **USHER - ED MIRVISH & CAA THEATRE**

Ed Mirvish Enterprises Itd | Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

 Maintained a welcoming environment by positively engaging with over 100 patrons per performance, communicating important information to the audience, and resolving any conflicts or issues that a patron might encounter.

#### **OFFICE ASSISTANT**

Vaughan Pediatric Clinic | May 2012 - August 2015

Aided with developing the clinic's digital face by scanning the patients' files into a
digital library, performing regular maintenance on the clinic's website via
Wordpress, and assisting with the development of their social media presence.